<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/content/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/content/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to use this Hugo theme ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/use-this-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/use-this-theme/</guid>
      <description>After downloading the theme, unzip the file and go to the &amp;rsquo;lightbi-hugo-master&amp;rsquo; folder. Open the folder in you editor and run the hugo build command as below.&#xA;hugo It will create a folder named &amp;lsquo;public&amp;rsquo; and in the same you can find the website created by Hugo from the contents from &amp;lsquo;content&amp;rsquo; folder and the theme. To check the website you can run the below command,&#xA;hugo server In the command prompt you can see that your website has started to build and it will normally available at &amp;lsquo;http://localhost:1313/&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Hugo Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/build-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/build-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>Hugo? It’s a fast and static website generator written in the Go language. Websites built with Hugo can be hosted anywhere from GitHub Pages to Amazon S3 without any database or other language dependencies.&#xA;First I started to use Hugo is for my Malayalam write up a blog wizbi tales (Malayalam is a language spoken in Kerala, India), After the initial learning curves, I loved it for simplicity and performance. And when I started this blog itself I didn’t think twice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Markdown ?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/markdown/</guid>
      <description>What is Markdown?&#xA;The Markdown Guide is a free and open-source reference guide that explains how to use Markdown, the simple and easy-to-use markup language you can use to format virtually any document.&#xA;Markdown is a lightweight markup language that you can use to add formatting elements to plaintext text documents. Created by John Gruber in 2004, Markdown is now one of the world’s most popular markup languages.&#xA;Using Markdown is different than using a WYSIWYG editor.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Basic Syntax</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/syntax/</guid>
      <description>Headings&#xA;To create a heading, add number signs (#) in front of a word or phrase. The number of number signs you use should correspond to the heading level. For example, to create a heading level three (h3), use three number signs (e.g., ### My Header). Heading level 1 Heading level 2 Heading level 3 Heading level 4 Heading level 5 Heading level 6 Paragraphs&#xA;To create paragraphs, use a blank line to separate one or more lines of text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>Hugo ships with several Built-in Shortcodes for rich content, along with a Privacy Config and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&#xA;YouTube privacy enhanced shortcode The youtube shortcode embeds a responsive video player for YouTube videos. Only the ID of the video is required, e.g.:&#xA;YouTube URL:&#xA;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3qHkcs3kG44 Shortcode:&#xA;{{&amp;lt; youtube 3qHkcs3kG44 &amp;gt;}} Rendered output: Twitter You want to include a single tweet into your blog post?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Host in Netlify</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/netlify-conf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/netlify-conf/</guid>
      <description>You can host your static website wth zero cost in Netlify.&#xA;Add the below netlify.toml in the root folder.&#xA;[build]&#xD;publish = &amp;quot;public&amp;quot;&#xD;command = &amp;quot;hugo --gc --minify&amp;quot;&#xD;[context.production.environment]&#xD;HUGO_VERSION = &amp;quot;0.82.0&amp;quot;&#xD;HUGO_ENV = &amp;quot;production&amp;quot;&#xD;HUGO_ENABLEGITINFO = &amp;quot;true&amp;quot;&#xD;[context.split1]&#xD;command = &amp;quot;hugo --gc --minify --enableGitInfo&amp;quot;&#xD;[context.split1.environment]&#xD;HUGO_VERSION = &amp;quot;0.82.0&amp;quot;&#xD;HUGO_ENV = &amp;quot;production&amp;quot;&#xD;[context.deploy-preview]&#xD;command = &amp;quot;hugo --gc --minify --buildFuture -b $DEPLOY_PRIME_URL&amp;quot;&#xD;[context.deploy-preview.environment]&#xD;HUGO_VERSION = &amp;quot;0.82.0&amp;quot;&#xD;[context.branch-deploy]&#xD;command = &amp;quot;hugo -b $DEPLOY_PRIME_URL&amp;quot;&#xD;[context.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who am I ?!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/who-am-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/post/2020/jan/who-am-i/</guid>
      <description>Who am I ?! This is the most asked question in my life. Yet no clear answer has yet been found.&#xA;As a child, the answer to this question was simple. Say my name to the question of who. Aha ..! Simple and beautiful. In that answer, parents and siblings in adolescence. I thought to myself that the answer was too clear.&#xA;When I started asking myself this question at a young age when I was beginning to recognize many things, I began to feel that the answer was becoming less clear.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
